ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Administration Program Files. (Box 23)
  - Eff. Collective Bargaining Skills 03W020 Public 10/8-10/9/03 Henderson/Rebholz Cancelled, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Prep for Collective Bargaining 04W040 Public Program 11/2-11/3/04 Henderson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Interest Based Bargaining 04W036 Public Program 10/27-10/28/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Increasing Effectiveness 04W031 Public 9/21-9/23/04 Henderson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Contract Language: Working Within It, Making It Work for You 04W030 Public, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 76)
- Administration Program Files. (Box 24)
  - 9/20 SHRM Classroom 04W007 Public 2/6/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - SHRM Inc. and L9P Report 04W007, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1st Annual Niagara Frontier SHRM Conf 04W009 American Sales Company, Inc 9/22/2004 Henderson (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Workers at Risk 04W019 Public Program 11/4/04 Johnson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Workers at Risk 04W018 Public Program 10/7/04 Johnson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Assertive Grievance Handling 04W017 Public Program 9/22/04 Johnson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Mid -Contract Bargaining 04W016 Public Program 9/21/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Globalization and Labor's Response 04W015 Public Program 9/15/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Health Care Bargaining 04W014 Public Program 9/14/2004 Johnson Cancelled (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Strategic Campaign Training 04W013 CSEA- Region 9 Johnson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Internal Mediation Skills Training 04W011 University at Buffalo 8/16. 17 and 19. 2004 Henderson (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Buddy to Boss 04W010 Seneca Nation of Indians 7/14 and 7/16/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration: The Basics of Advocacy 04W020 Public Program 11/15/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Combating Privatization 04W021 Public Program 1/18/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Conducting Effective Meetings 04W022 Public Program 2/4/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Broadcasting Labor's Message 04W023 Public Program 3/30/05 Johnson Cancelled, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Member-to-Member Conflict 04W024 Public Program 4/12/05 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Arbitration: The Basics of Advocacy 04W025 Public Program 4/26/05 Johnson Cancelled, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Effective Contract Language 04W026 Public Program 5/11/05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Organizing and the Law 04W027 Public Program 12/8/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Better Business Writing 04W029 Seneca Nation of Indians 8/31-9/1/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Sexual Harassment 04W035 Plumbers Local 22 1-17-05 Johnson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Effective Grievance Handling 04W038 Public Program 4/28/05 Henderson, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Labor Relations Law 04W037 Public Program 4/13-4/14/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Investigation Tools and Techniques 04W039 Public Program 5/19/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Visiting Delegation 04W041 World Connect 8/26/04 Wheaton, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Contract Language: Working 04W042 HealthNow New York 9/27/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Labor Relations Law 04W043 HealthNow New York 9/9-9/10/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Project Management Skills 04W044 Public 10/19-10/20/04 Henderson (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Project Management Communications 04W045 Public 11/9-11/10/04 Henderson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Employment Law for Managers 04W046 Public 11/18/04 Henderson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Sexual and Workplace Harassment.. 04W047 Public 12/2/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Gathering Project Mgmt Requirements 04W048 Public 2/15-2/16/05 Henderson Cancelled, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Project Management Software 04W049 Public 3/2-3/3/05 Henderson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Effective Grievance Handling: Form 04W050 HealthNow New York Inc. 2/23/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Training Workers as Foremen 04W051 IBEW LU 41 10/4/04-11/8/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Public Sector Law 04W054 New York Power Authority/Niagara BR 11/16-11/17/04 Henderson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Issues and Prevention: Sexual/Workplace 04W055 Public Program 12/9/04 Henderson Cancelled, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Co-Chair EDTP, ETC and ETS 04W056 UAW Ford 11/22/04 Suggs, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Contract Language Workshop 04W057 CWA Local 1168 10/26/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Would We Hire Us? 04W058 New York State Dept of Labor 11/9/04 Henderson/Rebholz, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Prevent Workplace Harassment 04W061 Erie County Water Authority 11/29/04 and 12/15/04 Henderson, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Steward Training 04W062A and B USWA LU 135 Dunlop Tire Plant) 11/11/04 and 11/13/04 Johnson, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Employment Maintenance 04W063 UAW Ford 11/29-12/3/04 Fleron/Suggs, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - National Civil Rights Conference 04W065 National Civil Rights Conference 12/3-12/4/04 Suggs, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Effective Discipline: Best Practice 04W066 Chautauqua and Erie Telephone Corp 1/6/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Legal Issues for Mangers 04W067 Chautauqua and Erie Telephone Corp 3/3/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Future of Labor Forum #1 4W068 Public 1/21/05 Johnson, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Supervising for Success 04W069A Public Program 3/1/05-3/22/05 Henderson, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- Faculty files Rebholz, Yvonne. (Box 25)
  - Tops Mkts, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Media and Comm Skills Workshops-Buffalo Labor Studies Students Debate + Library Research Skill, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Printers, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Local 4 Hotel Employees and Restaurants Employees Unions, 1991-1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Union Reps (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - UAW (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Community Resource Team Basic Needs/Economic Opportunities and United Way Memorandum + Liaison Team Contract List, 1996- 2000 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Outcome Funding Prototype Orientation Briefing Basic Needs + Economic Opportunity, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Project ICE, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Carol Kates (Folder 1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Carol Kates (Folder 2 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Faculty-Rebholz-Supervisory Studies, 1991-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Rebholz-Supervisory Studies (2), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Workforce of Future, 1992-1997 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - HR Mgmt, 1993-1997 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Program Leads, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Yvonne Dev. Studies, 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Young Workers, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Wkplc Violence, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Workers' Struggles, 1988-1996 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Workers Comp, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Work Organization, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Work and Spirituality (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Work and Family, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Women's Issues, 1986-1996 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Welfare Reform, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Video Production (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Training, 1994-2000 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Time Mgmt, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Technology, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Teams, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Supervision, 1991-2001 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Substance Abuse, 1984-1995 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Study Skills/ Wkplc Comm, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Study Circles, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Stress, 1989-1995 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Docs Related to Adult Education + Jobs (Folder 1 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Misc. Docs Related to Adult Education + Jobs (Folder 2 of 2), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Administration Program Files & MTLS. (Box 26)
  - 2002 Fall Forum (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Online Forum 2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Fall Forum 2000 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 2000 Spring Forum (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Workplace (Diversity), 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Netter Seminars 1008, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 1998 Spring Forum (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 1998 Fall Forum Regis. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - New Diversity Registrants, 1998-2000 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Netter Tapes, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - In Voices (Peels), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Diversity Renewals, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Workplace Diversity Network 1997-98 F/Y Financial Info, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Workplace Diversity Network 1996-1997 Financial Info, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Workplace Diversity Network 1995-96 F/Y Financial Info, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Workplace Diversity Network 1994-95 F/Y Financial Info, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers- Accounts Payable, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - The Workplace Diversity Network Participant Roster, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Netter Seminar 501- 8601 Income and Expense Reports, 1992-1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Netter Seminar 50-8601 Fliers and Informational Packets, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Netter Seminar 501-8601 Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Documents About The Workplace Diversity Network, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Netter 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Issues of The Network Newsletter- The Workplace Diversity Network: A Project of Cornell/ILR and the National Conference, 1995- 1996 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Netter '92, 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Old Netter, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - The Workplace Diversity Network Future Planning Session + Docs. Related to Conflict, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - The Workplace Diversity Network, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - The Workplace Diversity Network, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - The Workplace Diversity Network Spring Forum, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - 1994 Netter Seminar N. Amer. Economic Integration: Examining the Implications (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - 1994 Netter Seminar, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Richard and Alice Netter Seminar: The African American Male and the Workplace, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - EDSTP/NYS Dept Economic Dev 93W019 Unions and the High Performance Workplace November 16 and 17, 1993 Various, 1993- 1994 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Unions and the High Performance Workplace- Brochures and Extension Registration Forms, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Administration Program Files & MTLS. (Box 27)
  - Work/Life Balance Issues in the Workplace, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - 1997 Fall Forum The Workplace Diversity Network Making the Organizational Case for Diversity + A Framework for Building Organizational Inclusion, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - The Workplace Diversity Network Fall Forum 2000 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 1997 Fall Forum The Workplace Diversity Network Making the Organizational Case for Diversity (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - 1998 Fall Forum The Workplace Diversity Network and Other Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - 1997-1998 Fall Forum The Workplace Diversity Network Making the Organizational Case for Diversity and Other Reports Related to Diversity (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - WDN 199 Fall Forum Materials, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Masters 1999 Sp. Forum (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - WND Bibliography 3rd Ed, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Spring Forum 2000 Dialogue (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Atlanta Fall Forum 1998 Originals (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - (Bibliography) Resources to for Workplace Diversity Guide to Info, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Fall Forum 1997 Originals (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - hd Doc Follow-Up to 1998 Fall Forum Attendees (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - 1998 Net Originals (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - August 1-7, 2001 Reader's Forum (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Fall Forum 2000 Originals (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Brown, Nellie Personnel-Reg. Faculty Resume, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Blair, George Personnel-Reg. Faculty Resume, 1993-2005 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Campagna, Dennis Personnel- Reg. Faculty Resume, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Fleron, Lou Jean Personnel- Reg. Faculty Resume, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Grogan, Regina Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1987-2001 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Henderson, Pamela Personnel- Reg. Faculty Resume, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Rebholz, Yvonne Personnel- Reg. Faculty Resume, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Suggs, Clifford Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 1981-2000 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Whalen, Charles Personnel- Reg. Faculty Resume, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Wheaton, Arthur Resume Only, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Wheaton, Arthur Personnel- Adjunct Instructors, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Woods, Susan Personnel- Reg. Faculty Resume, 1986-1999 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Weller, Kristine Adjunct Faculty, 1999-2004 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Williams, Betty Personnel- Adjunct Instructors (I/C or Firms), 2001 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Yudess, Jo Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (I/C or Firms), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Zahm, Marilyn, 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Zazycki, Frederick Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (I/C or Firms), 1999-2005 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Zelawski JR, Richard G. Personnel - Adjunct Instructor, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Independent Contractors, 1993-2008 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Pending - Credit Instructor Approval, 2002-2004 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Weinstein, Rosemarie Personnel- Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 2000 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Michael A. Wawrowski, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Sherri Leronda Wallace, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - James E. Walling, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Vellake, Angelo A. Personnel - Adjunct Instructor, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Valutis, Marsha J. Personnel - Adjunct Instructors (on Payroll), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Eugene Thomas, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Stulmaker, Mark Adjunct, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Sugarman, Steven R., 1999 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Swarts, Susan Personnel - Adjunct Instructors, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Tarbox, Michelle Personnel - Adjunct Instructor, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Mary Lou Purtan Roy, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Diff. Course Approvals, 1994-1998 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Administration Program Files. (Box 28)
  - 2000 AIS Manual - Binder to Workbook 99W401C Ford UAW Buffalo 9/99 - 2/00 Fleron, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 2000 AIS Manual - Slides to PowerPoint 99W401D Ford UAW Buffalo 11/99 - 2/00 Fleron, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 2000 AIS Manual - ARS Expansion 99W401E Ford UAW Buffalo 10/99 -1/00 Fleron, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 2000 AIS Manual - Instructional Games 99W401F Ford UAW Buffalo 9/99 - 1/00 Fleron, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 2000 AIS Manual - Extras 99W401G Ford UAW 9/99 - 1/00 Fleron (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 2000 AIS Video 99W401H Ford UAW 5/31/00 - 11/17/00 Fleron (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Electric Industry Strategic Plng 99W402B Cornell University Buffalo 10/5/99 Fleron, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Diversity Proposal 99W403 Ford UAW NPC Detroit, MI 9/1/99 Fleron, 1988-1999 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Dev. - Manual Development 99W500B American Axle and Manufacturing 12/1/99 Grogan, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - NYC Off Campus Program 99W501 Diversity Section 8/10/99 Henderson, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Labor /Mgmt Facilitation 99W052 (a) New Era Cap/CWA 8/25/99 Carpagna, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - L/M Facilitation 99W502B New Era Cap / CWA 14177 10/7/99 Campagna, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Planning Retreat (CU) 99W503 Cornell Climate Committee 7/27/99 Henderson, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Relation Structure 99W600 Comparison / DaimlerChrysler 11/01/99 Fleron, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W001 UAW-Ford - BLACK Lake 7/24/00 - 7/28/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W003 UAW Cleveland 8/21/00-8/25/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W004 UAW-Ford - BLACK LAKE, MI 9/10/00-9/14/00 Fleron Cancelled, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W002 UAW-Ford BLACK LAKE 7/31/00-8/4/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W005 UAW-Ford - NASHVILLE 9/25/00-9/29/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W006 UAW - Ford LIMA 10/30-11/3/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Employment Maintenance D 00W007 UAW - Ford DETROIT 00W007A 11/13/00-11/17/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Employment Maintenance 00W008 UAW Ford ATLANTA 11/27/00-12/1/00 Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - E2 Educ. For Empowerment 00W009 AAM-UAW NOMMOS 9/11/00 and 9/14/00 Fleron Grogan Cancelled, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - E2 Educ. For Empowerment 00W010 AAM-UAW NOMMOS 10/9/00 and 10/12/00 Fleron/Grogan, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - E2 Educ. For Empowerment 00W011 AAM-UAW NOMMOS 10/30 and 11/2/00 Fleron/Grogan, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - PEL 00W013 UAW-GM Region 9 8/7/00 - 8/10/00 Fleron/Wheaton, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - PEL 00W014 UAW-GM Region 9 9/18/00 - 9/21/00 Fleron/Wheaton, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - PEL 00W015 UAW-GM Region 9 10/23/00 - 10/26/00 Fleron/Wheaton, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - PEL 00W016 UAW-GM Region 9 12/11/00-12/14/00 Fleron/Wheaton, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - UAW-Ford AIS 00W017 10/9/00 - 10/13/00 St. Louis Fleron, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Labor Union and the Internet 00W018 Public/Erie One BOCES 10/10/00 Lipsitz, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Labor Unions and the Internet 00W019 Public/Erie One BOCES 10/11/00 Lipsitz, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Drug and Alcohol Abuse @ Workplace 00W020 Labor Health 9/22/00 L9/15/00 Lipsitz, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - SHRM Certification 00W021 Public 09/11/00 - 11/7/00 Grogan, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Western Region Program Activity, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - The Basics: HR Overview 00W023 Public 8/9/00 Henderson, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Retaining Valued Employees 00W024 Public 7/19/00 Henderson Cancelled, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Retaining Valued Employees 00W025 Public 8/23/00 Henderson, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - The Basics: HR Overview 00W26 Public 7/12/00 Henderson, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Effective Feedback and Other Mgt. Dev. 00W027 Nabisco 7/22/00 Henderson Cancelled, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Effective Feedback and Other Mgmt. Dev. 00W028 Nabisco 8/19/00 Henderson Cancelled, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Effective Feedback and Other Mgmt. Dev. 00W029 Nabisco 9/16/00 Henderson Cancelled, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Administration Program Files. (Box 29)
  - WNY L?M Forum: Prospering Thru 99W255 Partnership-- Public 6/2/00 Whalen Cancelled (Folder 1 of 2), 2000 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - WNY L?M Forum: Prospering Thru 99W255 Partnership-- Public 6/2/00 Whalen Cancelled (Folder 2 of 2), 2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - 6/2 Audience Goals and Schedule (including program planning sheet) ( conferences round table details), 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence W/ Fed, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 6/2 Expenses, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 6/2 Notes on: Program Materials (including nametags) (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 6/2 Promotion A (Except Fed Mailing Lists), 2000 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - 6/2 Promotion: 3 Mailing Lists to Fed, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 6/2 Site, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - 6/2 Sponsors, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 6/2 Speakers, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Connections 99W199 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/24/00 (3:30- 11:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Connections 99W240 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/25/00 (7:70-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Connections 99W241 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/25/00 (3:30-11:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Connections 99W242 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/28/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Connections 99W243 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/28/00 (3:30-11:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Connections 99W244 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/29/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Connections 99W245 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/29/00 (3:30-11:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Connections 99W246 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 3/1/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Connections 99W247 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 3/1/00 (3:30-11:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Connections 99W248 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 3/2/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Connections 99W249 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 3/2/00 (3:30-11:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Connections 99W250 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 3/3/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Connections 99W251 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 3/3/00 (3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Problem Solving Thru Mutual Gains 99W252 National Assoc. of Women Business Owners 2/23/00 Campagna, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Finding Your Way around the Law Library 99W253 Buffalo Labor Studies Students 3/11/00 Lipsitz, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Steward Training for PACE 99W254 A/B/C Ithaca Cornell ILR 4/25/00 and 4/26/00 Lipsitz, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Connections 99W171 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 1/31/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Connections 99W172 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/1/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Connections 99W173 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/4/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Connections 99W174 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/6-2/7/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Connections 99W175 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/7/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Connections 99W176 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/7-2/8/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Connections 99W177 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/8/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Connections 99W178 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/8-2/9/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Connections 99W179 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/9/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Connections 99W180 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/9-2/10/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Connections 99W181 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/10/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Connections 99W182 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/10-2/11/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Connections 99W181 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/11/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Connections 99W184 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/13-2/14/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Connections 99W185 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/14/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Connections 99W186 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/14-2/15/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Connections 99W187 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/15/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Connections 99W188 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/16-2/17/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Connections 99W189 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/17/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Connections 99W190 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/17-2/18/00 (11:30-7:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Connections 99W191 Outokumpu Copper, Bflo. Manufacturing Unit 2/18/00 (7:30-3:30) Grogan, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 48)